Guide to the The Inquiry Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Abstracts, Precis, Notes, 1902-1918, undated; Series IV
  - Abstracts of Miscellaneous Area Studies
    - Spitzbergen: "Spitzbergen, Geography and Economic Conditions." (Box 26, Folder 26)
      Proof sheets of printed British Foreign Office report.
  - Miscellaneous Research Notes
    - Austria-Hungary
      - Miscellaneous research notes on Austria-Hungary. (Charles Seymour) (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - "Inventory [of Inquiry material]: Austria-Hungary." (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Eastern Europe: Research notes on Lithuania and Poland from German sources; and memorandum on Rumanian finances. (E. Krehbiel) (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Great Britain
      - Research notes on opinion in Great Britain on various issues of peace-making. (E. Krehbiel) (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - Research notes on opinion in Great Britain on various issues of peace-making. (E. Krehbiel) (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Luxemburg: Research notes on "Luxemburg." (L. Steefel) (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Schleswig: Research notes on North Schleswig. (L. Steefel), Received 1918 September 16 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Turkey: Research notes on criticism of Inquiry reports on Turkey. (L. H. Gray), 1918 June 10 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Western Front: Research notes on various articles dealing with the general subject of the Western Front. (E. Krehbiel) (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Yugoslays: Research notes on nationalistic activities of Yugoslays. From French article "La Grande Serbie" by Denis. (E. H. Krehbiel) (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Abstracts, Precis, Translations
    - Adriatic
      - Article from Quarterly Review, vol. 224, p. 327. (Box 26, Folder 37)
      - "The Racial and Political Problem in Adriatic Lands." Abstracted from "The Problem of the Adriatic," by J. A. R. Marriott, Nineteenth Century and After., 1915 December (Box 26, Folder 38)
      - Summary of The Question of the Adriatic by C. Maranelli and G. Salvemini. (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Africa
      - L'Afrique Francaise-Bulletin Mensuel du Comite de l'Afrique Francaise, p. 41., 1918 January-March (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - "The Future of Africa" by Secretary of State Dr. Solf, from Koelnische Zeitung., 1917 December 22 (Box 27, Folder 41)
        Includes newspaper clipping.
    - Albania
      - Memoranda on Albania by M. Tourtoulis [in French]. (Box 27, Folder 42)
        With precis and English translation and covering note from Isaiah Bowman to Walter Lippmann, 1918 Jan 11.
      - Miscellaneous articles and interviews on Albania. By E. Durham, L. Dominian, C. Woods, F. S. Noli. (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Alsace-Lorraine
      - "History of Alsace and of Lorraine." Serial in Annales Politigues et Littéraires. Summary and Translation by W. A. McLaughlin. [incomplete] (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - "Demography of Alsace-Lorraine." By Paul Meuriot, in Journal de la Société de Statistique de Paris LV., 1914 October (Box 27, Folder 45)
        Slightly abridged, with covering note to Isaiah Bowman from W. Notestein.
      - "The Right of Self-Determination of Alsace-Lorraine." Vossische Zeitung., 1918 October 28 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - "Ill Treatment of Alsatians and Lotharingians by the 4th Regiment Grenadier Guards" (Box 27, Folder 45)
        From statements by Alsatians and Lotharingians taken prisoners on Oct. 23.
      - Newspaper clipping (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - Research notes from British journals. (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - "The German Peace and the Question of Briey-Longwy" by H. Hauser, in L'Action Nationale. Translated by W. H. Hobbs., 1918 April 25 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Antwerp: "Antwerp, Its Geographical Position and Industrial Importance." By H. Praesent, from series Kriegsgeograplusche Zeitbilder., 1915 (Box 27, Folder 47)
      Summary.
    - Australia: "Notes on Remarks Made by Premier William M. Hughes of Australia on the Attitude of his Government to the After-War Settlement.", 1918 Hun 7 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Austria-Hungary
      - Abstract from article in La Grande Encyclopedie. (Box 27, Folder 49)
      - "Austrian Concessions to Italy." Statement of Dr. von Bethmann-Holding to the Reichstag. New York Times., 1915 May 19 (Box 27, Folder 50)
      - Austria-Alpine Provinces. Abstract from The Continent of Europe. By Lyde. (p. 358) (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - Research notes by Walter Lippmann on "The Extent of the Slavic Movement in Austria" by R. S. Sieger (Graz) in Deutsche Politik., 1918 January 11 (Box 27, Folder 52)
      - "Attitude of Emigrants From the Trentino Now Working in Mines of the United States." Letter from C. O'Neill, Secretary of the Central Pennsylvania Coal Producers' Association, Altoona, Pennsylvania., 1918 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Bagdad Railway: Article on The Bagdad Railway by P. Rohrbaek, published by Wiegandt and Grieben, 1902. (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Czechoslovakia
      - Memorandum on "Corridor Between Czecho-Slovakia and Jugo-Slavia," from General Headquarters, American Expeditionary Forces, Second Section, G-S., 1918 December 18 (Box 27, Folder 55)
      - Miscellaneous abstracts from articles on Czech nationalism. (Box 27, Folder 56)
      - Copy of letter from T. Masaryk to Commissar Tchitcherin, Moscow. (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - China: Miscellaneous abstracts of articles and interviews on China. (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Danzig: Abstract of article "The Commerce of Danzig" by O. Nunsterberg, Agricultural Association of Berlin, 1906. Abstract by M. G. Marsh(?)., 1918(?) January 28 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Economic Aspects of the War: Memorandum on a plan of study of some economic aspects of the war (The Commercial Empire of the East)., 1918 April 10 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - French Troops from North Africa: Abstract of article "La Force Noire" by Colonel Mangin, published by Hachette, Paris, 1911. Abstract by Major Bonsal, War College. (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Freedom of the Seas: Abstracts from The Sovereignty of the Sea by T. W. Fulton, published by Blackwood and Sons, Edinburgh and London, 1911. (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Germany, Pacific Colonies: "The Pacific Colonies of Germany" by Secretary of State, Dr. Solf. Illustrierte Zeitung., 1918 July 11 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Great Britain: "British Labor's War Aims." New York Evening Post., 1918 January 14 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Greece: "Greek Proclamation with Reference to Naval Warfare." Jahrbuch des Volkerrechts, Vol. 2, part 1, pp. 481-494. (Box 27, Folder 65)
      Translated by L. Kohn.
    - International Law: Miscellaneous abstracts and bibliographical notes on international law by M. O. Hudson., Received 1918 November 10 (Box 27, Folder 66)
      Covering memorandum from M. O. Hudson to David Hunter Miller, 1918 Feb 15.
    - Italy
      - Abstract: "Italian versus Slav in the Adriatic," from On Great Serbia by Krompotic. (Box 27, Folder 67)
      - Miscellaneous abstracts and reference notes on Italian irredenta. (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Japan: Miscellaneous research notes, bibliographical notes and abstracts on Japan. By S. K. Hornbeck. (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - League of Nations: "Extract from a letter from Lord Bryce.", Received 1918 March 12 (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - Lebanon: "Treaty of Lebanon" by E. Nord, from Jahrbuch des Volkerrechts II (1914), Part II, pp. 365-403. Translated by L. Kohn., 1918 July 3 (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Lithuania: "The Lithuanian-Baltic Question," by Dr. Gaigalat, of the Prussian Landtag. Translated by the Lithuanian Committee. (unrevised) (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - London Conference of 1871: "The Preliminaries of the Conference of London" from the Revue d'Histoire Diplomatique, Vol. XXIII. Translated by E. Haas. (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Italy: Various texts of the "Pact of London" between Italy and the Allies, April 26, 1918. Statistical abstracts of districts included within the line of the treaty. (Box 28, Folder 74)
    - Mittel-Europa: Article: "The Threat of 'Mittel-Europa,' by T. G. Frothingham., 1917 July (Box 28, Folder 75)
      Printed.
    - Most Favored Nation Clause: Abstract from article "Most Favored Nation Clause: American Interpretation" by C. L. Jones, Annals, XXXII, p. 121. (Box 28, Folder 76)
    - Near East: Near East in Parliament, House of Lords, News of Persia., 1917 February 23 (Box 28, Folder 77)
    - Poland: Abstract: United States Weekly Report on Central Powers, no. 28. Editorial in the Koelnische Zeitung and other comment with regard to Poland., 1918 January 14 (Box 28, Folder 78)
    - Russia: Abstract: Russia in Asia, Vol. VII. The Relations of Russia towards Japan Especially with Regard to Korea. By Krahmer. (Box 28, Folder 79)
    - Samoa: Abstracts on Samoan Condominium. By Walter Lippmann. (Box 28, Folder 80)
    - Self-Determination
      - Chronoligical List of Those Cases of Changes of Sovereignty in Which the Right of the People Involved to Self-Determination Has Been Recognized. (Box 28, Folder 81)
      - A Few Remarks Upon Professor Schafer's Map of Euporean Races and States. (Box 28, Folder 81)
    - Schleswig: Memorandum on Schleswig. (translation) (Box 28, Folder 82)
    - South Africa: Abstract of speech by General Smuts in London, on "The Native Problems in South and Central Africa and the Military Training of Natives as They Affect War Problems and the Peace Settlement.", 1917 May 22 (Box 28, Folder 83)
    - South America: Reports and notes on maps of South America (Box 28, Folder 83a)
    - Turkey: Miscellaneous abstracts on Turkey. (Box 28, Folder 84)
    - Ukraine: Article: "Ukraine and Ukrainians." By Nicholas Ceglinsky. (translation), Received 1918 March 9 (Box 28, Folder 85)
      With covering letter to F. C. Howe, Commissioner of Immigration, from J. J. Ardan, Norodna Wola - The People's Will, the leading Ukrainian triweekly.
    - Yugoslays: Abstract: "The Yugo-Slays" from Language and the Sentiment of Nationality. By C. O. Burk in American Political Science Review, Vol. X, No. 1., 1916 February (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Latin American Division of The Inquiry: Bibliographic Synopsis (Box 28A)
- Miscellaneous Printed Materials, 1913-1927, undated; Series V
  - Miscellaneous French Propaganda Material. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "The Ruthenian Question in Galicia." By W. Lutolawski and E. Romer. Paris., 1919 June (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "The Economic Situation of Japan." United States War Trade Board, Bureau of Research. Washington., 1918 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Personalities -LIBYA" [Great Britain] Admiralty War Staff, Intelligence Division., 1917 August (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Rating the Several Sovereign Nations on a Basis Equitable for the Allotment of Representatives to a World Parliament." By H. Laughlin. Reprinted from The Scientific Monthly., 1916 December (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - "International Rivers." By C. C. Hyde. Washington., 1918 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "The Question of Slesvig-Holstein." [Great Britain] Admiralty War Staff, Intelligence Division., 1916 December (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "Tunisia - Tribes." [Great Britain] Admiralty War Staff, Intelligence Division., 1916 August (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - "The Turkish and Pan-Turkish Ideal." By Tekin Alp, [Great Britain] Admiralty War Staff, Intelligence Division., Undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - "Conspectus of Special War Activities of Executive Departments and Independent Establishments." Washington. [oversize], 1918 August 14 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - "The Pioneer Fringe." By Isaiah Bowman. Reprinted from Foreign Affairs., 1927 October (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - "The Crescentic Dunes of Peru." By A. E. Douglass. Reprinted from Applachia., Undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - "Edad de los Fosiles Peruanos y Distribucion de sus Depositos en la Republica." By Carlos I. Lisson. Lima, Peru., 1913 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Photographs, 1915-1918, undated; Series VI
  - Panoramic photographs of Italy, the Italian-Austrian border, and the Italian-Yugoslavian border, 1915-1918, undated (Box 30, Folder 1-47)
  - Panoramic photographs of eastern France and the French-German border, 1916-1918 (Box 31, Folder 48-73)
  - Panoramic photographs of France; also miscellaneous and unidentified photographs, 1916-1918 (Box 32, Folder 74-132)
- Oversize Maps (Miscellaneous Printed Materials), 1856, 1868-1919
  The series, Maps, includes various types of maps, graphs and charts. The material is arranged by continent and nation. Areas include Austria Hungary, Germany, Poland, North and South America, Africa and Asia.
  - Austria-Hungary
    - Photostats
      - Iron ores (Folder 33A)
      - Agricultural statistics (Folder 33A)
      - Tatsachliche Zu - and Abnahme der anwesenden Bevolkerung (Folder 33A)
      - Linguistic Districts (Folder 33A)
      - Religions (Folder 33A)
      - Harta etnografica a Transilvaniei de N. Mazere, 1909 (Folder 33A)
      - Transitions between Czechoslovak Polish… languages within Austria-Hungary (Folder 33A)
      - Ethnography of Austrian Silesia, compiled by Arctowski (Folder 33A)
      - Fed. Great Austria on basis of ethnic boundaries (Folder 33A)
      - Development of Bohemian Crown Lands according to Hanau, 1918 (Folder 33A)
      - Magyars on the Hungarian Plains (Folder 33A)
      - Series of graphs representing nationalities in Austrian & Hungarian Government divisions, 1918 (Folder 33A)
      - Parliamentary representation by nationalities, 1918 (Folder 33A)
      - Railways in Bosnia, 1913 (Folder 33A)
      - Four maps (negative & positives) by Prof. M. Atkins, University of Chicago (Folder 33A)
      - The New Danubian Monarchy (Folder 33A)
      - Number of Emigrants…in Hungary in 1911 (Folder 33A)
      - Transit Trade across Austria-Hungary (Folder 33A)
      - Foreign Trade of Austria-Hungary, 1918 (Folder 33A)
      - Percent of race in "Corridor" districts (Folder 33A)
      - Production of chief cereals in territories claimed by Yugoslavs (Folder 33A)
      - Language rights of all nationalities (Folder 33A)
      - Claims of Czechs (Folder 33A)
      - German language rights (Folder 33A)
      - Federalization, I & II (Folder 33A)
      - Districts with preponderance of Rumanians in Austria-Hungary (Folder 33A)
      - Number of small, medium, and large agricultural holdings in Austrian lands (Folder 33A)
      - Boundaries of geographical regions in Hungary (Folder 33A)
      - Visitors to Trieste (Folder 33A)
      - Commercial Hinterland of Trieste, 1911 (Folder 33A)
      - Czecho-Slovak complex (Folder 33A)
      - Population density and language in Rumanian region. De Martonne (Folder 33A)
    - Map
      - Territory taken from Rumania by Austria-Hungary and Bulgaria, 1918 (Folder 33A)
    - Base Maps
      - Head Form, Austria-Hungary (Folder 33A)
      - Languages (Folder 33A)
      - Stature (Folder 33A)
      - Territorial acquisitions of the Hapsburgs (Folder 33A)
      - Map showing certain historic divisions in Austria-Hungary (Folder 33A)
      - Population density (Folder 33A)
      - Yugoslav Trialism (Folder 33A)
      - Federalized within exisitng boundaries (Folder 33A)
      - Suggested Corridor connecting Yugoslav & Czechoslovak States (Folder 33A)
      - Percent of Serbs, Croats, and Slovenes combined interritories claimed by Yugo-Slavs (Folder 33A)
      - Showing line of Pact of London as identical with line mentioned in the Armistice - by Loebeck and Storck (Folder 33A)
      - Percent of Roman Catholics…in the territories claimed by Yugo-Slavs (Folder 33A)
      - Percent of population unable to read & write in territories (Folder 33A)
      - Density of population in territories… (Folder 33A)
      - Density of population in Austria-Hungary, Italy, and Balkans (Folder 33A)
      - Series of photostats of Tyrol, showing history etc. (Folder 33A)
      - Tracing, Danube Basin (Folder 33A)
  - Germany
    - Photostats
      - Karte des Memel-Pregel - and Weichselstromgebietes in Preussen (Folder 33B)
      - Hohenschichten Karte der Preuss. Seenplatte… von Dr. A. B Bludau (Folder 33B)
      - Geol. karte zum Handbuch fur den deutschen Braunkohlenbergbau, 1911 (Folder 33B)
      - Imports and exports, by A.A. Young (Folder 33B)
      - Agricultural statistics, Germany. By U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1918 (Folder 33B)
  - Poland
    - Photostats
      - Religions (Folder 33C)
      - Carte ethnographique Pologne Prussienne (Folder 33C)
      - Distribution of forests in basins of Vistula and Nieman (Folder 33C)
      - Karte des Ostrau-Karwin-Krakauer steinkohlen-revieres by W. Petrascheck (Folder 33C)
      - Frontiers, linguistic, etc. (Folder 33C)
      - Percent of Greek Orthodox population in Government of Chelm, 1897-1907-1917 (Folder 33C)
      - Jewish population (Folder 33C)
      - Increase of the percent Polish population (Folder 33C)
      - Germans in Congress (Folder 33C)
      - Government of Suwalki, population, 1910-1914 (Folder 33C)
      - West Prussia and Posnania; gain and loss of Polish population, 1918 (Folder 33C)
      - Polish territories in North Hungary, compiled by Arctowski (Folder 33C)
      - Ethnographic map of eastern territories of Poland (Folder 33C)
      - Mineral map of Poland and adjacent territory by M. Roessier, 1918 (Folder 33C)
      - Hydrographic map, by Arctowski (Folder 33C)
      - Schematic representation of Galicia (Folder 33C)
      - Ethnographic map of Ugor Russians by S. Tomashivsku (Folder 33C)
      - Skizze der Oberschlesischen Erzlagerstatten, by Arctowski (Folder 33C)
  - Asia, Africa, South America, Pacific
    - Map V, Central Russia in Asia, colored to show majorities and pluralities, minorities (Folder 33D)
    - Map V, oversheet, showing hypothetical changes… (Folder 33D)
    - Growth of population, 1897-1915, Russia in Asia, photostat (Folder 33D)
    - Base map of China, colored to show railways (Folder 33D)
    - H.O. chart 1500, colored to show Guano Islands in Pacific (Folder 33D)
    - Base map, Pacific, including America, by Hudr. Office 1918, colored to show possessions (Folder 33D)
    - Photostat, Pacific Islands (Folder 33D)
    - S. America, base map, 1:2,000,000, sheet S. C-D/23-24, preliminary edition (Folder 33D)
    - Africa: photostat colored to show temperature and area suitable for white colonization in central Africa (Folder 33D)
    - Africa: 3 photostat colored to show climate (Folder 33D)
    - Africa: 2 Distribution of Mohammedans-Christians (Folder 33D)
    - Africa: 7 Base map, Cape to Cairo route (Folder 33D)
    - Africa: 2 photostats to accompany C.F. Andrew's French North Africa, boundaries-agricultural data, population (Folder 33D)
    - Africa: Map accompanying report of M. Leplae on Belgian Congo (Folder 33D)
  - Africa
    - (Accompanying Professor Fennimore's report) (Folder 34D)
    - Photostat map of Central Africa (2 copies) (Folder 34D)
    - Colored map of Central Africa showing areas of concentration of endemic sleeping sickness (also 2 photostats of the map) (Folder 34D)
      Also includes 2 photostats of the map.
    - Colored map of Central Africa depicting location of different species of Glossina (Tsetse Flies) (Folder 34D)
    - Photostat map of Central Africa - showing areas of concentration of sleeping sickness and of Glossina (Folder 34D)
      Also shows isolation camps and examining posts.
    - Photostat map of East Africa - showing concentration of Trapanosoma Rodesiense (East African sleeping sickness) (Folder 34D)
    - Photostat - provisional map of East Africa protectorate (Folder 34D)
    - Colored map of Northeast - showing distribution of tsetse flies (Folder 34D)
    - Colored map of Northeast Africa showing areas of concentration of endemic sleeping sickness (Folder 34D)
    - Colored map of Northeast Africa showing location of different species of tsetse flies (Folder 34D)
      Also includes 2 photostats of map.
    - Colored map of Northwest Africa showing location of different varieties of tsetse flies (Folder 34D)
      Also includes 4 photostats of the map.
    - Colored map of Northwest Africa showing areas of concentration of endemic sleeping sickness (Folder 34D)
    - Colored map of South Africa (region) showing areas of concentration of endemic sleeping sickness (Folder 34D)
    - Colored map of South Africa (region) showing location of different species of tsetse flies (Folder 34D)
    - Photostat map of West Africa - showing location of the Stegomyia (tropical) mosquito (Folder 34D)
    - Photostat of West Central Africa - showing location of various diseases (Folder 34D)
    - Photostat map of West Central Africa - showing concentration area of Baleri (Folder 34D)
    - Photostats:
      - Map of Belgian Congo showing dispersion of the Trypanosoma (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Northern Belgian Congo showing location of different species of the Glossina (tsetse fly) (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Cameroun showing distribution of sleeping sickness and the tsetse fly (Folder 34D)
      - Map of French Equatorial Africa (Chad Region) showing locations of different species of the tsetse fly (Folder 34D)
      - Map of German East Africa showing distribution of small livestock and of the natives (Folder 34D)
      - Map of German East Africa showing distribution of the tsetse fly and the state of the cattle plague as of March 31, 1913 (Folder 34D)
      - Map of German East Africa showing native population as of March 31, 1913 (Folder 34D)
      - Map of German East Africa - survey map (Folder 34D)
      - Map of German East Africa showing various diseases located in the Shirati District (Folder 34D)
      - Map of German Southwest Africa - survey map (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Gold Coast - Blackwater Fever (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Mozambique showing the distribution of tsetse flies (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Nigeria showing cases of Blackwater Fever (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Southern Nigeria showing distribution of the Genus Glossina (tsetse fly) (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Nyasaland to accompany return of cases of Blackwater Fever (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Nyasaland showing the sleeping sickness in the area in the Dowa District (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Portuguese East Africa showing location of different species of the tsetse fly (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Northeast Rhodesia showing location of various species of tsetse fly and where sleeping sickness was observed (Folder 34D)
      - Map of North Eastern Rhodesia (and Nyasaland) showing areas of concentration of various species of Glossina (tsetse fly) (Folder 34D)
      - Map of North Eastern Rhodesia with location of different species of Glossina (tsetse fly) (Folder 34D)
      - Map of North Western Rhodesia (Northern area) location of Glossina Morsitare, distribution of cattle, and other information (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Southern Rhodesia with location of Try panosomiasis (sleeping sickness) in the area (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Senegal showing the location of Glossina Morsitans (tsetse fly) (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Sierra Leone showing the distribution of Genus Glossina and sleeping sickness (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Sierra Leone - survey map (district headquarters, utilities, etc.) (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Spanish Guinea showing the location of sleeping sickness in the area (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Northern Sudan with location of sleeping sickness at Ragaa and location of Genus Glossina (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Southern Sudan with location of sleeping sickness and location of the Genus Glossina (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Togo - survey map (location of county seat, navigation lines, etc.) (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Uganda showing the distribution of sleeping sickness (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Uganda depicting the various boundaries (International, Provincial, and District) along with the Government stations (Folder 34D)
      - Map of Uganda Protectorate (Folder 34D)
      - Map showing distribution of undulant fever throughout the world (Folder 34D)